So you are Tiararose?
It is an honor to meet you,
Forest Fairy King.
You may call me Keith.
The forest fairies seem to have
taken quite a liking to you.
I am grateful and delighted
to have their favor.
Lift your head.
Interesting.
Tiara, your soul is most unusual.
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
Tiara in the Sleeping Forest
It's a very unstable soul,
but also beautiful.
And it smells very nice.
King Keith...
Perhaps this is what you smell.
No "King" needed. Simply call me Keith.
But...
Do it.
A-All right...
What an egotistical fairy king!
I see. Cookies, eh?
Oh? These contain your magic, I see.
Oh, yes. It's not strong magic,
but I'm able to put it
into the sweets I make.
Either way, they're quite good.
King Kei—
Keith.
I'm glad you like them, Keith.
Good.
Unlike humans, fairies are free, you know.
We go by whatever name we like.
So it seems.
I wish I could live like a fairy, as well.
What's this? Is something troubling you?
No.
Humans have many things
that tie them down.
I was just thinking about
how difficult that is.
Relax.
If anything ever happens,
I'll be your strength.
Thank you.
Thank you for making time
to meet with me today.
I should be thanking you.
You're always the one helping me out.
Oh, not at all.
Come to think of it, it's unusual
for you to turn to Lady Icilla
for matters unrelated to work.
I'm referring to the hair accessory.
I want to give Tiara
the best there is, after all.
You were even up all night
coming up with a design yourself.
You knew about that?
I am your attendant.
I envy Lady Tiararose.
The man she loves
is so genuinely fond of her.
Your Highness, it's Tarmo.
Enter.
Pardon me.
What is it? Where's Tiara?
So you are a future queen, then?
That isn't set in stone yet.
I'm only the prince's fiancée.
Humans are always so difficult.
He's the future king, isn't he?
What's he like?
Yes. Prince Aquasteed is very kind
and has the unwavering
support of his people.
He's a far more wonderful man
than I deserve.
Wait, what time is it?!
I-I need to go back!
Where is the exit?
I'll take you there.
Huh?
My... room?
Leave it to a fairy king.
He used that difficult
teleportation spell so easily.
Tiara!
Who are you?!
Get away from Tiara!
You must be Aquasteed.
I'd be a better match
for you than this guy.
Please stop that, Fairy King!
A fairy king?!
I had no idea you were a fairy king.
I apologize for lifting
my blade against you.
Very well. I forgive you.
I'm in a good mood right now.
But Tiararose is my fiancée.
Getting so close to her
seems an undignified thing
for a fairy king to do.
Well, look at that.
He sure loves you a lot, Tiara.
It's what you did that caused
his misunderstanding, Keith!
No matter.
I'll take my leave for today.
If life gets too hard for you,
call me anytime.
I'll help you as thanks for the cookies.
Keith...
U-Um...
Um, I...
Tarmo told me.
The forest fairies took you away, right?
Y-Yes! I'm so sorry for making you worry!
I wouldn't get angry with you over that.
No, he's definitely angry.
Do you think I'm angry, Tiara?
Honestly... I'm so jealous.
P-Prince Aqua...
That's why I'm angry, you know.
The name.
Name? Prince Aqua...
I called the fairy king "Keith"
without any title.
Is Prince Aqua saying he wants me
to do the same with him?
But is that even allowed?
Maybe when it's just the two of us...
A-Aqua.
Right answer.
You did very well.
Thank you, ma'am.
Well, that will be all for today.
Oh! Prince Aquasteed!
It looks like you're done.
Yes. Lady Tiararose
is such a brilliant student
that she completed six months'
worth of work in one month.
All that remains is one week of
lectures on fairies, and we're finished.
I see. You're so brilliant, Tiara.
Thank you! I'll study my hardest!
By the way, do you have
some time after this?
What? Me?
Yes. I want you to see my work
up close and understand it.
But I'm only your fiancée.
I have little knowledge
of your kingdom's affairs.
Not a problem.
Even as queen, you aren't likely
to have much involvement in my work,
but knowing about it isn't a bad thing.
Understood.
I'll do my best to be useful
to you, Prince Aqua.
You've been working
too hard every evening.
May I suggest you stop
for tonight and rest?
There's nothing I can do
to be useful to Prince Aqua yet.
But you've been working
more than hard enough.
Still, I had no idea
that Lady Icilla was so frequently
in his office, even if only for work.
Lady Icilla is only fourteen,
yet she already does such diligent work.
How can I be useful to him?
Oh, it smells lovely!
I'm sure your magic sweets will
relieve the prince's exhaustion.
Thank you. I'll try my best.
Morning, Tiara!
You're making sweets?
You can have these!
Oh, nuts and flowers?
Philine, open your mouth.
These flowers from
the forest fairies are edible.
It's delicious! It has its own natural
sweetness and isn't bitter at all!
Right?
Wow, you baked this for us, Tiara?
Yes.
Since you two are working so hard,
I wanted you to have it.
I'm happy you thought of us.
Let's take a short break.
All right.
You always make such
delicious sweets, Tiara.
It tastes wonderful!
It really is exquisite.
I'm so glad you all like it.
Come in.
Pardon me.
Oh? Is this from you, Lady Icilla?
It's the latest cake recipe
from our family chef.
Since you're here now, I wanted
to offer you something sweet,
but maybe this was poor timing.
Not at all!
Please, don't worry about that.
It's such a beautiful cake.
I love sweets, you know!
You do look so happy when you eat sweets.
I could watch you forever.
I'll bring some more next time.
What a luxurious cake.
Which one do you prefer, Prince Aquasteed?
Well...
What's there to think about?
Tiara's tastes much better.
Fairy King!
I'll come again for some more.
I know I told you before
that I would rather you
didn't touch my fiancée.
Oh, did you?
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
You're still eating that cake?
You don't even care much for sweet foods.
The ones Tiara makes are different.
Honestly...
Why couldn't you just say
hers tasted better, then?
I need to keep Lady Icilla in a good mood.
Especially while she's in the castle.
Yes, that is true...
If Lady Icilla's mood is soured,
the sea fairies will feel it,
and the seas will rage.
But as long as she's happy, the seas
will share their bounty with us.
More, please.
What? Again?
The "dripping with handsomeness" CG!
Why did I forget about that
until just now?
It was the only sample still revealed
for the sequel before I died,
from an event where Prince Aqua
is walking in the ocean on a date,
falls in, and gets all wet.
Prince Aqua looked so hot.
Wait, no! He was on
a date with the heroine!
It was an event that progressed
his romance with Icilla!
I can't guess when that event will happen.
I should be fine as long as Prince Aqua
doesn't go into the ocean with her...
What? The ocean?
Yes. I'm going to inspect
Lady Icilla's ocean.
It seems a new species of coral
has appeared there.
Oh, no...
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing.
Tiara.
You don't need to hold back with me.
But it's official business
for you, isn't it?
I can't be selfish about...
Don't finish that sentence.
I won't stop until you tell me.
Please... Please don't go into the ocean!
All right. I won't go.
Huh?
I'll have Elliot do the inspection.
You're more important to me, after all.
Prince Aqua...
So Master Elliot will accompany you
for today's inspection?
Yes. Sorry about that.
Understood.
Will Master Elliot be here soon?
He's with the knights right now,
so we'll go get him.
Come with us, Tiara.
There's a lovely rose garden
along the way.
Shall we see it together?
I'd love to!
Oh, how pretty!
They're beautiful!
If you see any you like,
you can pick them.
Are you sure?
Of course. Lady Icilla,
you're also welcome to them.
Thank you!
Oh, look at these!
These white roses would match
Lady Tiararose's hair perfectly!
Lady Icilla!
Prince Aquasteed!
Prince Aqua! Are you all... right...
Dripping with handsomeness!
No... But that event was
supposed to happen at the ocean...
Is the game's power—
the power of the events—absolute?
Is it impossible for me to change
the progression of the game?
Tiara!
Now I've done it. After I said
I wouldn't run away anymore...
But I can't help feeling anxious.
Is Prince Aqua's heart
still leaning toward me?
How can I become stronger?
It's okay.
If I just keep looking up,
the tears will dry in no time.
Keith?!
What's this? Did he make you cry?
No, he didn't!
But your heart is crying.
If you're suffering, just come to me.
I keep telling you, it's not like...
Remember what I told you?
Fairies are free.
Tiara, I'm coming in.
She's not here?
Those are...
That fairy king?
Tiara...
Hey, it's Tiara!
Welcome back, King!
Keith! What is the meaning of this?!
Now, stop howling.
I don't think you realize this, Tiara,
but your face looks awful.
Huh?!
Lie down and rest a while.
Not enough sleep?
That's bad for your skin!
Er, um...
Take me back! I'll rest in my own room!
I think not.
You know forest fairies
are capricious, don't you?
But I have my own...
Even as vulnerable as you are, I didn't
think you'd fall asleep that easily.
You must have really felt terrible.
I'm gonna take a nap with Tiara!
A consort loved by the forest fairies, eh?
And the sea fairies like
that human called Icilla, don't they?
Humans can be a headache,
but those sea fairies are a pain, as well.
They grow extremely attached.
That one time a girl
they loved was in trouble,
the ocean was stained red,
the fish vanished, and the coral withered.
When was that again?
How many centuries ago?
We've searched the entire castle,
but we couldn't find her.
How could he abduct Lady Tiararose?
What is that fairy king thinking?
The royal family's forbidden texts
may tell us where the Forest
Fairy King can be found.
Wait here for a while.
Understood.
Damn it. Where is it?
I get why there are so
many records of the oceans,
but there are far too few for the forest.
"The path to the Forest Fairy King's
throne begins in the castle"?
In the castle?
The queen's chamber?
Why would it be there?
Fairy King!
Hey. You seem rather desperate.
You don't think maybe that's because
you abducted my consort?!
Well, I wasn't planning to at first...
but I changed my mind.
Fairies are capricious, you know.
Enough joking around!
I'm not joking.
I'll be taking her.
Hold Me... Tighter
I'm happy that Prince
Aqua says he loves me,
but... that's also why I'm scared.